all right so this is the $15 million
house that I'm staying here in Madrid
been here for about 2 weeks I forgot how
America's like honestly this shit's fire
this is probably one of the craziest
airbnbs I've ever stayed cuz I've stayed
in houses all around the world so let's
go check it
[Music]
so I've been on this side of the world
probably for about 2 weeks and I'm
already going to be on this side
probably for another month and a half
we're going to London Africa Dubai and
we're going to be staying in the
craziest airbnbs so you want to see more
houses like this make sure you hit that
subscribe button this is probably one of
the most beautiful houses I've ever
stayed in myself I live in a house that
is probably a tenth of this one it's
literally like like half that right
there which is fine so this house has
indoor pool outdoor pool gym saunas
theme room everything you're probably
wondering how do I afford this house
well it's with trading and you guys
might think I'm going to show you right
now that I made a million dollars I
actually lost $68,000 in the last two
days that I've been here because I'm not
used to the time zone so this is plus 6
or 7 hours from Miami SO trading in
London is like trading New York here New
York is London here but that's not what
this video is about this video is about
this [__] crazy ass house so let's go
guy that lives here and owns his house
can I say who I think it is pretty sure
by the time we say this were long gone
yeah I it's definitely a Colombian so
you guys can do your math you guys can
add literally there's bulletproof doors
bulletproof window Escape rooms you can
do the math on who you think owns this
house so the first thing you see when
you come through the backyard is this
pool now this is a ginormous pool but
it's not an outdoor pool it's actually
an indoor outdoor pool so it actually
goes like right into the house right
into the middle of the living room and
like this whole Spa section that they
have here that room up there is actually
my room master bedroom I've been staying
for 2 weeks I love it so coming in
through here is the spa hear a little
bit of echo but it's like the waterfall
that they have going on here where are
the lights oh there you go all right so
these are the lights which is pretty
[__] sick so you come over here and
you have the pool that pretty much goes
from outside to literally inside so
right now we have the cage down I don't
know why it makes no sense there's a
running waterf and then this actually
goes to one of the six living rooms that
this one entire house has and you also
have like a little alley way that way
which is like where one of the other
offices are super sick you have hot
plunge cold plunge so when you get out
from the jacuzzi you go right into the
cold plunge and through the back and
forth sauna which is probably one of the
hottest saas that I have ever gone into
my whole entire life got a steam room
that it says
noar can't use it it's broken it's
broken okay and this entire area almost
feels like a resort as you come out here
you have steam room SAA jacuzzi and then
you have these bathrooms with these
[__] bathrooms make you feel like
you're in like a spa shower area you
have like look at that [__] what the
[__] is that like how many shower look
what is that six shower heads I don't
know doesn't make sense this whole
entire house has like an indoor outdoor
Vibe the whole entire house so this is
what we just left right now which is so
right here there's literally like four
rooms that way there's two rooms that
way craziest [__] ever right we came out
this way and then literally that way
it's just like a never ending journey of
I don't know what the [__] I've SE in a
bunch of airbnbs but this [__] is crazy
look up you literally can see never
ending stairs to the upside never ending
stairs to the downside you have a pool
table down there craziest thing you're
about to enter my favorite spot in the
house and where I have spent the
majority of the time so this is the pool
the indoor outdoor pool pretty cool how
you can see it right here and then we're
here which is my office so this is
pretty much what I've been working for
the last 2 weeks it's a very rustic old
school vibe that I've never really been
into but being here kind of I like it
because I pretty much got accustomed to
this whole entire area and it's
something new and you look over here and
you're probably wondering what the [__]
this is I look short you're making me
look short yeah right I'm 62 right so
this right here is the winery so this
the person that [__] built this [__]
literally put a I think it was like 200
bottle Winery pretty much go down the
stairs right there I actually haven't
even been here yo this is kind of
[__] sick and you ask me bro Dam it's
kind of chilly in here look look at this
guy look at
this all right so this is the winery
right so this is the winery down was
second from here when I buil my house in
the next 2 years I'm going to do this
this is pretty cool coming up this way
you have the gym so this is uh that's on
underground level three I think so it's
pretty much whole entire gym you have
everything you need go in and out coat
plunge hot tub and
then see okay ladies pretty lit so you
have hot plch go plun SAA steam room
then full- blown J coming this way you
have living room you have demo Trader
one demo Trader 2
[Applause]
so this is uh pretty much like the third
living room have a dining table there
pretty much just entire living room here
this like another path to the outside
which looks pretty cool so yeah
literally in this house I've been
staying with the whole entire team for
the last two weeks we got the legend
Sensei the biggest demo Trader of them
all so all right for those you guys that
don't know say don't forget baby yeah
but tell them about the challenge so
we're doing a challenge for 100k I
already won but no it it is a fitness
challenge whoever gets the the best abs
in two months okay show them your abs
right now okay so that Sensei ABS right
now right so we bet $100,000 whoever's
going to have the most Abs from two
months from yesterday right let me show
them but you can't so I I'm not letting
him see my
apps who do you think who do you think
won e morning baby all right all right
whatever all right so coming this way so
if you see that way that house is
literally [__] I'm talking
about there's like 10 rooms out and then
there's still another floor and then two
floors under so make sure you watch
around to stick this whole entire video
cuz this [__] is lit yeah I'm going to
take this guy's money bro this guy
[__] up we really bet $100,000 on so
coming over here you have a living room
the formal living room you have the door
which really sleep with the door open
just in case somebody wants to come in
take the watch door's open you take it
we have all of our camera gear lights
and stuff we do like portable podcasts
all the time but coming this way it's
going to be office number two and
remember I'm 6'4 look how big this
[__] door is like this is literally a
ginormous door into the office there's
no door knobs there no locks you just
kind of push it and you go right in so
coming into this area is going to be
office number two so this pretty much I
guess the more open one because you can
see people if they were to come in you
can look right over the living room you
can look right into the pool saw a
Jacuzzi can look right into the kitchen
from here you can look right outside
pretty much everywhere and obviously you
have your stuff this is where Sensei has
been trading the majority of the time
and I don't know what the hell this is
but it pretty much controls the whole
entire house from this area that tells
me to leave that the owner of the house
this is his office cuz he controls
pretty much everything through there so
coming this way little bathroom over
here oh this is this is the weirdest
thing ever I don't know if you guys have
ever experienced this [__] but whoever
uses there's a square [__] toilet
honestly if I were to do anything on a
square toilet I wouldn't want to flush
it yeah so this is like a square fet as
well I don't I don't get it but then it
moves fin another the Escape Route I'm
not asking any questions so coming to
the outside over here I ly wish we would
have done this a little bit earlier but
we leave tomorrow so I just decided to
do this really quick this is the outside
of the house in the front all right so
coming this way you have pretty much all
these different sectors of the house
which look kind of cool because you can
literally see how like the kitchen
living room 25 guest room 17 are all
divided in different sectors then you
have the Underground Level
super sick uh come over here you kind of
have this whale thing I don't know what
this means maybe this guy was a big
crypto guy and he was a whale and he
moved the market that's why he has this
whale tail here I have no questions I
have nothing to say want to see
something really cool that I thought it
was really unique so this is the front
of the house when you come out to the
front you have this right here this
right here is going to be a double-sided
mirror so security when they stay here
at night pretty much just post up in
here
with the double-sided mirror that they
can see right out so you can literally
see right out for the section here
anybody were to come into the house this
is kind of like I wouldn't want to say
random but it has a ho ass playground
how we were letting people in take our
watches they got to get past Security
First we can't just make it easy you
know what I'm saying if you get past
security then [__] it you can just take
it you know security is trash Security's
right there you see all so this area
over here is like the outdoor playground
area it's kind of confusing what this is
I'm not really trying trying to walk
over there cuz it's dark care of the
dark can you zoom in over there for me I
don't got to walk over there you got
like a playground swing bunch of [__]
and you have the garage so that garage
over there is where they keep like super
cars or something they're not letting us
go in there so lucky I don't got the
keys now I take the car but yeah the
house goes on that way for a really big
space this is the whip we've been using
lately Suzuki kidding it's not the car
clean lady's car so something that I
really do like about the house is going
to be like the indoor outdoor Vibe like
you always feel like you're in the house
but you also feel like you're outside
house so now I'm going to show you guys
the other guest rooms the master bedroom
and then the rooftop I completely forgot
we had a [__] rooftop all right so we
just obviously came through this B
section over here we already saw the
gear so this is dining table section
three there's also a bigger one outside
which actually I completely forgot to
show you guys but love this section
right here you can sit 10 people awesome
com over here we've had a chef for the
last two weeks the best thing I could
have ever done Chef has been absolutely
cooking it in here [__] [__] up
making breakfast lunch dinner and also
snacks juices everything so I like how
this is sectioned off because if you
we're having a private dinner we can
close that door and then we can close
that door and then none of the smell
gets out there's no interaction between
the kitchen and what's going on outside
go over here got like a little breakfast
table area coming over here we have
living room 10 with bathroom 25 and then
you have kind of this chill section
another dinner table or coffee table
whatever section you want to call this
you have these super dope ambient lights
which is pretty much what the whole
house consists of of these ambient
lightings and you have a treadmill which
is what I've been using for the last
couple of days you have this outdoor
section here which is really really
cool which actually we actually haven't
used coming to this outdoor section you
have another table to pretty much eat do
whatever you want you have guest room
six I think this one is which is
actually really cool cuz you have this
whole patio to yourself well actually
there's another room over there you have
it to yourself oh you have this area
here I forgot to show you guys so this
is definitely a party house whoever owns
this [__] definitely goes crazy cuz look
they literally have a whole bar area
that's a whole Bart tending table and
there's a whole DJ section or dance
floor section that they just created
specifically for that oh oh over there
buto we forgot to show the [__]
vegetables they like gr sh over
there I don't know what they grow but
they're growing something so this is
obviously really nice area look like the
second time I've actually been out here
so many other places in the house this
right here let me make sure I don't hit
myself with the glass so this is
actually the filmmaker's bed this is
where he's been sleeping for the last
two weeks thank you man I'm super
appreciated you're welcome bro it's what
you deserve man for 3 years of hard long
work keep doing it and then you
eventually you'll get a I get a blanket
yeah you get a blanket this way more
rooms that way what show them show do
you have a mess in your room I mean I'm
a filmmaker what does that mean oh my
God this is probably the most organized
so this is clearly not my room this is
filmmaker room so you guys can see this
is a this looks like a like like a Lab
look at this you have a bunch of [__]
look like a hacker bro with all this
[__] gear but it's kind of cool has
this corner section you can see more
into like the playground area and the
garage of the super cars we can't even
show them the bathroom don't don't even
do that bathroom's actually pretty clean
this area over here same exact thing
this is this chief of marketing's room
let's see how this room is
wow would you look at that chief of
marketing look how clean this is so I
have one of my chief of marketers that I
always bring out with me when I travel
look how well organized this guy is this
is why you're going to keep wonder why
yeah I do wonder why maybe because he's
not a filmmaker what does that have to
do with anything oh we're going to show
you guys sens have you seen the the kai
thing LeBron James you know what I'm
talking about Michael
Jordan my God LeBron
James LeBron James
this the sensus room so you guys have an
idea how this guy travels this guy
travels with one two three four and then
five
bags is he a is he a woman or is he a
man women travel a lot of [__] hey see
all right soing this
way sorry yeah yeah sorry yeah yeah yeah
yeah
yeah all right all right so continuing
this way I'm show you guys my room right
now which is [__] crazy because my
room has a bulletproof door so this
section right here go downstairs to the
spa oh bro we have to go all the way
down to the gym all right so this is my
room so little bit on the messy side
because I just woke up from a nap we're
just getting organized so we oversee the
beautiful pool backyard everything then
this is where [__] gets kind of crazy
you have a ginormous bathroom with a
ginormous [__] closet but it's not
just times one it's [__] x two we
have the same thing the times two we
look it over here then you have the
whole entire thing this way by the way
this is where one of the hidden doors
are look this right here private access
right this is the hidden door C go in
but
look like literally get get closer so
like they can feel like solidness
so you have three locks here two locks
here two locks here two and two so when
they lock it it literally boom and it's
literally like look at this you're not
breaking in through the store at any
given CR but I'm W breaking through that
window though no no no no you can't cuz
that [__] goes down too look you want to
see oh [__] I see it yeah that's just
bulletproof too bro look at this the
[__] craziest thing ever so I I
literally clicked the button by accident
and then this [__] [__] started
coming down it scared the [__] out of me
and I stopped it so oh my God whatever
the whole rooftop section up there
honestly don't even want to go up there
going to take you guys to the gym which
is a lit pool table here didn't even you
it one time like didn't even use this
thing at all and this is where things
got a little more confusing there's
another door in there and there's hidden
stairs this
way [__] hidden stairs the go I I
haven't wanted to touch it I don't want
to be that guy verus I respect people's
space so this literally a whole gym like
locker room section here where it kind
of looks like and then you have the
jump so this is where I've been getting
shreding for the last two weeks BR
Sensei don't got [__] on my competition
so this where pretty much I've been
chopping up sense hitting every single
type of workout you can tell that we're
underground it's like that's the office
up there where we were at earlier so
yeah this is the gym pretty full gym you
got everything you need and after this
house I'm actually going to be getting
another one like this in South Africa in
Cape Town because we're going to be
there for about 3 weeks and then I'm
going to be getting the biggest one that
I've ever gotten in Dubai I'm going to
try and stay in the Palm get one of the
biggest ones or somewhere around there
so you guys want to see more videos like
this make sure you guys hit that like
And subscribe button hopefully my trade
can come back from being in $68,000 that
I took of a loss by trading here
hopefully I can make it back usually I'm
making about you know 3 to half minut
milon a week with training on a good
week I've been losing for about a month
and a half consistently which [__]
sucks so hopefully me trading in
different time zones can actually make
things back but it's kind of just like a
little house tour show you guys like a
raw version of what living with me kind
of would be in a way because obviously
I'm with all the boys the whole team is
here and I don't know thought it'd be
kind of cool maybe you guys would like
it but if you guys want to see more
videos like this and you guys like this
concept make sure you guys hit that like
And subscribe button and comment down
below and let me know who do you think
is going to win the challenge me or
Sensei who who the [__] do you think is
going to win I mean you already have abs
so thank you bro Lally just losing
weight I needed that thank you all right
see you guys in the next video